# **AntonyWuth**

### contact

100 Eucumbene Dr Duffy, ACT, 2611 Australia

+61 (0) 414 254 157 +61 (02) 6287 4506

ajw@pobox.com

Linux Solaris

### IT administration

Oracle Database
Data Communications
TCP/IP Networking
ICT Metric's
Internet Services
DNS
HTTP
ICT Security

### **ICT Design**

SOE Security Gateway environments Network Web Applications

### **ICT Audit**

Security
Firewall review
Networks
Log management and
review

### Languages

Perl Java PHP VGL

### **IT Management**

Continous Intergration /
Dev
Systems Monitoring
Network Monitoring

### personal history

I worked under contract as a theatrical technician as well as running a private help desk before becoming a contract programmer in February 1998. I have supported and developed for life critical systems such as the Sample Manager Laboratory Management product at the Australian Water Quality Center (AWQC). I am proficient in a number of different programming languages, with the skills to rapidly learn new languages as required. I am experienced in the installation and maintenance of Oracle systems running under AIX, Solaris, Windows and Linux. I have considerable experience in network installations specialising in TCP/IP. I have been involved in the specification and roll out of secured public access systems. I have also worked with both small business and large enterprises to implement reliable, secured and cost effective networks.

#### 0.0.1 Staff Management

Throughout my career I have been required to manage staff, a role I am comfortable in filling. Whilst at the Department of the Environment I was initially responsible for managing a small development team, and then progressing to a section of sixteen IT professionals with a variety of skills. I enjoy the interaction that comes with a management role and look forward to continuing this aspect of my career.

#### B

LAH BLAH BLAH

**employment** 

employment

### 2013-Now Australian Government, Department of the Environment can-

berra, Australia

### **Director Platform Services Section Duties:**

- Lead and manage a diverse team of ICT professionals.
- Manage multi-million dollar operational and project budgets
- Project management of both internal and externally delivered systems.
- provide advice, participate and manage ICT procurement activities including large tender processes. Including large whole of government activities.
- Assist in new strategic initiatives both directly and via participation in steering committees and working groups.
- Manage external providers and consultants.
- Implement and manage mixed Linux and Windows servers.
- Participate in key audit processes including implementation of recommendations.
- Deliver key infrastructure projects:
  - Migration to new Secured intranet Gateway
  - Design and implementation of new MAN network design
  - Implemenation of system configuration management system (pupept)
  - Oracle Database and infrastructure upgrades

2008-2013 Australian Government, Department of Sustainability, Environment, Water, Population and Communities Canberra, Australia Director Environmental and Business Information Systems Section

### **Duties:**

- Lead and manage a diverse team of ICT professionals.
- Manage multi-million dollar operational and project budgets
- Project management of both internal and externally delivered systems.
- Assist in new strategic initiatives both directly and via participation in steering committees.
- Manage external providers and consultants.
- Implement and manage mixed Linux and Windows

## 2004-2008 Australian Government, Department of Environment and Heritage Canberra, Australia

### **Database and Internet Officer**

### **Duties:**

- Develop, implement and manage Internet applications.
- Implement and manage mixed Unix (Solaris) and Windows servers.
- Provide support for web based applications to both internal and external clients
- Manage relationships with external providers and consultants.
- Manage APS level staff.
- Train and assist clients to effectively utilise information systems.

### 2002-2004 Cape3

Canberra, Australia

### Senior Analyst - Web Programmer

### **Duties:**

- Design of back-end databases, including integration with legacy systems.
- Implementations of designs in:
  - ColdFusion
  - Perl
  - HTML
  - PHP
- Assisting graphics designers to realise their vision.
- Design and specification of systems and network upgrades.
- Preparation of tender responses

### 1998-2002 Australian Water Quality Centre

**Boliver, South Australia** 

Page 3 of 5

### Analyst / Programmer

### **Duties:**

- Power Builder development
- Development of database reporting software
- Migration and cleansing of data from legacy systems
- Interfacing financial and laboratory systems
- Design and implementation of work scheduling systems
- Support for Sample Manager
- Maintenance and improvement of Laboratory Information systems
- VGL Programming

awards

2009 Secretary's Award Department of the Environment, Water, Heritage and the Arts

Awarded for sustained contribution towards realising the

**Department's outcomes** 

2007 Division head's Award Corporate Stratigies Division, Department of the Environment

Awarded for excellent management of the Department's mid-range database, infrastructure and web information

systems

2007 Division head's Award Corporate Stratigies Division, Department of the Environment

Awarded for excellentsupport to the Department's web in-

formation systems

### communication skills

**2013 Oral Presentation** 

Splunk live

Presented the Department's implementation of splunk as a security and log management system.

### education

2012	Splunk, search administration, installation		
2011	<b>Project Management Best Practice</b>	Dept. of Environment and Heritage	
2004-presen	004-presentOracle Database Administration and feature updatesoracle Corperation		
1999	<b>Oracle</b> Database Administration	Oracle Corperation, Canberra	
1999	Sample Manager Administrtion	LabSystems Australia, Adelaide	
1998	Sample Manager Advanced VGL Programmers, Sydney	gramming LabSystems	
1997	<b>Diploma</b> Diploma of Business Programming Computer Power Training Institute, Canberra  C, COBOL, Visual Basic, SQL, business applications, operating systems and network operating systems		
1993	Year 12 Certificate	St Edmunds College, Canberra	

### interests

professional: ICT & physical security, solution design, systems automation, process quality improvment personal: cycling, fish-keeping, home-automation, electronics, embedded programming, wood working.